<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- This file contains iLabjack documentation -->
<?xml-stylesheet href="../../../doc/xmldocumentation.css" type="text/css"?>
<xmldoc>
  <moosapp>

     <info>
        <name>iLabjack</name>
        <organization>ENSTA Bretagne</organization>
        <date>2015</date>
        <authors>
           <author>Clément Aubry</author>
        </authors>
        <licence>MIT</licence>
     </info>

     <documentation>
        <synopsis>
          Interface to Labjack U3 application.
          This app use exodriver for labjack, install it following http://labjack.com/support/linux-and-mac-os-x-drivers
          In the example folder of the exodriver archive, you could find subfolders containing example programs for differnet labjacks. For each, you could find u3.h,u3.c (u6.h,u6.c, etc). These c files are an easy interface to use labjacks. Some modifications are needed to use those interfaces in your app.

          copy u3.c, u3.h in the sources folder, rename u3.c under u3.cpp and change the code to be C+ compliant (remove goto and labels, I know it seem neird but the original code is very clear). In cas of any doubts, see the diffs between u3.c from exodriver and u3.cpp from this app.
          Add u3.cpp (u6.cpp, etc) to SRC list in CMakelist.txt.

          You could modify, extend this app to be more general using easy functions declared in u3.h
        </synopsis>
        <interface>
           <subscriptions>
              <!--
              <moosvar>
                 <varname>EXAMPLE_VAR_IN</varname>
                 <vartype>string</vartype>
                 <varinfo>description of the MOOSVar</varinfo>
              </moosvar>
              -->
              <moosvar>
                 <varname>SET_FIOX_STATE</varname>
                 <vartype>string</vartype>
                 <varinfo>These variable ask the app to change FIOX state. The string had to be formatted as : "FIO=x;VALUE=y;" with x the number of the FIO output and y the value</varinfo>
              </moosvar>

           </subscriptions>
           <publications>
              <!--
              <moosvar>
                 <varname>EXAMPLE_VAR_OUT</varname>
                 <vartype>string</vartype>
                 <varinfo>description of the MOOSVar</varinfo>
              </moosvar>
              -->
              <moosvar>
                 <varname>FIOX_STATE</varname>
                 <vartype>bool</vartype>
                 <varinfo>Published when FIOX has been changed as an acknowledgement. This data is a copy of previously received "FIO=x;VALUE=y;"</varinfo>
              </moosvar>

           </publications>
        </interface>
        <!-- if there is a bug or a special fact to know.. -->
        <optional-comments>
           The labjack easy function can connect to any (U3 for the moment) labjack connected to an USB device, no need to specify USB port.

           Support hot-unplugging of labjack, would be re-connected when re-plugged
        </optional-comments>
        <!-- if something can be improved -->
        <suggested-improvements>

        </suggested-improvements>
     </documentation>

  </moosapp>
</xmldoc>
